Finding Aid for the Collection of Television Film Scripts PASC.0074
UCLA Library Special Collections
- HENDERSON MONSTER (THE), (4/22/1979) (Box > 5)
- HER LIFE AS A MAN, (9/9/1983) (Box >150)
  Writers: Lakin, Rita; Rothman, Mimi
- HERE COMES SUMMER, (no date) (Box >238)
- HE'S NOT YOUR SON, (12/9/1983) (Box > 81)
  Writers: Collis, Alan; Friedl, Rob and Van Gores, A.
- HEY, I'M ALIVE, (1/22/1975) (Box >171)
- HIGH RISK, (2/14/1976) (Box >165)
  Writers: Carrington, Robert
- HIGH SCHOOL U.S.A., (5/11/1983) (Box >187)
  Writers: Lisenstock, Alan; Mintz, Larry
- HIGH SCHOOL U.S.A. 0, (2/29/1984) (Box >110)
  Writers: Proft, Pat
- HIJACKING OF THE ACHILLE LAURO (THE), (7/8/1987) (Box > 75)
  Writers: Collins, Robert
- HIS & HERS, (12/19/1983) (Box > 59)
  Writers: Kane, Arnold
- HISTORY OF WHITE PEOPLE IN US (PART I: IN SEARCH), (1/7/1985) (Box > 46)
  Writers: Mull, M.
- HIT LADY, (4/15/1974) (Box >105)
  Writers: Mimieux, Yvette
- HIT RADIO, (1/14/1994) (Box >209)
  Writers: Amann, David
- HOBSON'S CHOICE, (6/25/1982) (Box >156)
- HOBSON'S CHOICE, (12/12/1981) (Box > 92)
- HOLIDAY, (3/11/1996) (Box >217)
  Writers: Watson, Ara; Blackwell, Sam
- HOLLYWOOD WIVES, (7/26/1984) (Box >189)
  Writers: McCullough, Robert L
- HOLLYWOOD WIVES, (6/20/1984) (Box > 46)
- HOME FIRES BURNING, (7/15/1988) (Box > 67)
  Writers: Inman, Robert
- HOME FOR THE HOLIDAYS, (8/1/1972) (Box >111)
- HOME INVASION, (9/12/1996) (Box >219)
- HOME OF OUR OWN, A, (3/24/1975) (Box >170)
- HOME TO STAY: CONSENT, (2/18/1983) (Box > 5)
- HOMER AND THE WACKY DOUGHNUT MACHINE (SPECIAL), (3/11/1977) (Box >243)
  Writers: Fink, Mark
- HONKY-TONK, (2/4/1974) (Box >119)
- HONOR THY FATHER, (no date) (Box >176)
  Writers: Carlino, Lewis John
- HONOR THY FATHER, (no date) (Box >250)
- HOPE, (no date) (Box >249)
  Writers: Kennedy, Kerry
- HOSTAGE HEART (THE), (4/14/1977) (Box > 5)
- HOSTAGES, (4/27/1992) (Box >215)
  Writers: Sturgeon, Scott
- HOSTAGES, (1/27/1992) (Box >179)
  Writers: MacLaverty, Bernard
- HOT PURSUIT, (1/5/1984) (Box >169)
  Writers: Johnson, Kenneth
- HOT ROD, (3/2/1979) (Box > 77)
  Writers: Armitage, George
- HOW TO PICK UP GIRLS!, (no date) (Box >165)
  Writers: Crittenden, Jordan; Gethers, Peter
- HOW TO SURVIVE THE 70'S (SPECIAL), (11/18/1977) (Box >244)
- HUCKLEBERRY FINN, (2/10/1973) (Box > 5)
- HUCKLEBERRY FINN, (11/23/1974) (Box >170)
  Writers: Totten, Robert
- HUMAN FEELINGS, (4/10/1978) (Box >114)
  Writers: Bloomstein, Henry
- HUNTERS OF THE REEF, (3/1/1978) (Box >157)
- HURRICANE, (11/12/1973) (Box >143)
  Writers: Turley, Jack
- HUSTLER OF MUSCLE BEACH (THE), (1/3/1980) (Box >113)
  Writers: Smilow, David
- HUSTLING, (no date) (Box >195)
- I HEARD THE OWL CALL MY NAME, (8/29/1973) (Box >135)
- I KNOW MY FIRST NAME IS sTEVEN (PARTS I-II), (11/18/1988) (Box > 74)
  Writers: Miller, J. P.; Whitcomb, Cynthia
- I KNOW WHY THE CAGED BIRD SINGS, (2/13/1978) (Box >168)
  Writers: Thuna, Lee; Angelou, Maya
- I LED TWO LIVES, (5/11/1994) (Box >219)
  Writers: Rowell, Kathleen Knutsen
- I LOVE YOU...GOODBYE, (6/26/1973) (Box >140)
  Writers: Gould, Diana
- I MARRIED WYATT EARP, (no date) (Box > 24)
  Writers: Rapoport, I.C.
- I TAKE THESE MEN, (6/7/1982) (Box >182)
  Writers: Baer, Richard
- I WALK IN YOUR SHADOW, (12/13/1984) (Box > 46)
- I WANT TO KEEP MY BABY, (5/26/1976) (Box > 85)
- I WANT TO LIVE, (3/3/1981) (Box >164)
- I WANT TO LIVE, (1/5/1981) (Box > 47)
  Writers: Mankiewicz, D.M
- I WANT TO LIVE, (12/20/1982) (Box >140)
  Writers: Mankiewicz, D.M.; Cotler, Gordon
- I WAS A MAIL ORDER BRIDE, (3/19/1982) (Box >195)
  Writers: Zito, Stephen; Black, Stephen
- ICE CAPADES WITH KIRK CAMERON (Special), (no date) (Box >231)
  Writers: VILLANCH, BRUCE
- IF I WERE EIGHTEEN AGAIN, (4/11/1985) (Box >114)
  Writers: Hall, Barbara
- IF IT'S TUESDAY, IT STILL MUST BE BELGIUM, (4/1/1987) (Box >141)
  Writers: Eisenstock, Alan; Mintz, Larry
- IF THESE WALLS COULD TALK..., (4/26/1995) (Box >218)
  Writers: Savoca, Nancy
- IF THINGS WERE DIFFERENT, (6/8/1979) (Box > 47)
  Writers: Froehlich, B.
- IF TOMORROW COMES, (3/3/1971) (Box >106)
- IKE (PART I), (4/28/1978) (Box >165)
- IKE (PART II), (5/22/1978) (Box >165)
- I'LL TAKE MANHATTAN (PART III), (3/7/1986) (Box >141)
- ILLUSIONS, (8/10/1982) (Box >158)
  Writers: Cherry, Stanley Z.; Cherry, Carole
- I-MAN, (10/4/1985) (Box >182)
  Writers: Friedlander, Howard; Peragine, Ken
- I-MAN, (8/9/1985) (Box >182)
- IN BROAD DAYLIGHT, (9/25/1990) (Box >216)
- IN BROAD DAYLIGHT, (4/28/1971) (Box > 5)
- IN BROAD DAYLIGHT, (9/25/1990) (Box >173)
- IN DEFENSE OF KIDS, (5/10/1982) (Box > 47)
  Writers: Gallery, M.
- IN DEFENSE OF KIDS, (6/23/1982) (Box > 6)
- IN LIKE FLYNN, (1/18/1985) (Box > 71)
  Writers: Larson, Glen A.
- IN LOVE WITH AN OLDER WOMAN, (3/11/1982) (Box >142)
  Writers: Norell, Michael; Kaufelt, David A.
- IN LOVE WITH AN OLDER WOMAN, (no date) (Box >148)
  Writers: Norell, Michael
- IN SEARCH OF AMERICA, (8/17/1970) (Box > 79)
- IN SEARCH OF AMERICA, (7/24/1970) (Box > 88)
- IN SICKNESS AND IN HEALTH, (7/24/1991) (Box >173)
  Writers: Hines, Alan; Eliason, Joyce
- IN THE BEST INTEREST OF THE CHILD, (10/20/1989) (Box >127)
  Writers: Sitowitz, Hal
- IN THE CUSTODY OF STRANGERS, (10/22/1981) (Box >107)
- IN THE GLITTER PALACE, (7/30/1976) (Box >120)
  Writers: Ludwig, Jerry
- IN THE HEAT OF THE NIGHT, (11/5/1987) (Box > 65)
- IN THE LINE OF DUTY: A COP FOR THE KILLING, (5/17/1990) (Box >128)
  Writers: Rosenberg, Philip
- IN THE MATTER OF KAREN ANN QUINLAN, (2/28/1977) (Box >117)
- IN THIS HOUSE OF BREDE, (11/4/1974) (Box >158)
  Writers: Costigan, James; Godden, Rumer
- IN THIS HOUSE OF BREDE, (9/16/1974) (Box >174)
- INCIDENT (THE), (6/1/1989) (Box >186)
  Writers: Norell, Michael; Norell, James
- INCIDENT IN SAN FRANCISCO, (11/20/1970) (Box >162)
  Writers: Dozier, Robert
- INCIDENT ON A DARK STREET, (12/27/1971) (Box > 90)
  Writers: Neuman, E. Jack
- INCONVENIENT WOMAN, AN, (11/10/1990) (Box >124)
  Writers: Pielmeier, John
- INDECENCY, (3/23/1992) (Box >183)
  Writers: Sloan, Holly Goldberg; Jones, Amy
- INDICTMENT (THE): THE MCMARTIN TRIAL, (7/11/1994) (Box >203)
  Writers: Mann, Abbey; Mann, Myra
- INDICTMENT (THE): THE MCMARTIN TRIAL, (12/27/1993) (Box >211)
  Writers: Mann, Abby; Mann, Myra
- INFLAMMABLE, (4/4/1994) (Box >257)
  Writers: Smith, Mark Allen
- INMATES: A LOVE STORY, (3/3/1980) (Box > 92)
  Writers: Culver, Carmen; Hirsch, James & Delia Jordan
- INSIDE THE THIRD REICH, (1/30/1982) (Box > 47)
  Writers: Neuman, E.J.
- INTENSIVE CARE, (5/23/1994) (Box > 66)
  Writers: Stern, Sandor; Kahn, Jan Jaffe
- INTIMATE AGONY, (1/3/1983) (Box >147)
  Writers: DeRoy, Richard
- INTIMATE STRANGER, (9/17/1990) (Box >126)
  Writers: Fresco, Rob
- INTRIGUE, (no date) (Box > 15)
- INTRUDERS, (7/16/1991) (Box >210)
  Writers: Torme, Tracy
- ISABEL'S CHOICE, (4/13/1981) (Box >171)
  Writers: Hailey, Oliver
- ISHI: THE LAST OF HIS TRIBE, (1/1/1978) (Box > 85)
  Writers: Trumbo, Dalton; Trumbo, Christopher
- ISN'T IT SHOCKING?, (no date) (Box >101)
- IT (PART I), (12/16/1989) (Box > 68)
  Writers: Cohen, Lawrence D.
- IT (PART II), (2/5/1990) (Box > 68)
- IT HAPPENED AT LAKE WOOD MANOR (AKA: ANTS!), (5/27/1977) (Box > 71)
  Writers: Trueblood, Guerdon; Nelson, Peter
- IT HAPPENED AT LAKE WOOD MANOR (AKA: ANTS!), (6/24/1977) (Box > 98)
- IT WAS HIM OR US, (11/7/1994) (Box >240)
  Writers: Lawton, Richard
- JACQUELINE BOUVIER KENNEDY, (3/20/1981) (Box > 47)
  Writers: Gether, S.
- JAMES DEAN, (10/27/1975) (Box >169)
- JANE DOE, (9/24/1982) (Box > 6)
- JANE DOE (AKA "REMEMBER ME"), (no date) (Box > 52)
- JEALOUSY, (7/22/1983) (Box > 19)
- JENNIFER: A WOMAN'S STORY, (9/8/1978) (Box >154)
  Writers: Gregson, Richard
- JENNY, (1/23/1984) (Box > 20)
- JERICHO MILE (THE), (9/20/1978) (Box > 98)
  Writers: Nolan, Patrick J.; Mann, Michael
- JIGSAW, (11/2/1971) (Box > 94)
  Writers: Thompson, Robert
- JIGSAW, (12/30/1971) (Box >198)
  Writers: Thompson, Robert E
- JOE DANCER: THE BIG BLACK PILL, (7/11/1980) (Box > 86)
- JOE DANCER: THE BIG TRADE, (1/16/1981) (Box > 79)
  Writers: Waters, Ed; Alexander, E. Nick
- JOHNNY BELINDA, (6/8/1982) (Box >150)
  Writers: Milburn, Sue
- JOHNNY BELINDA, (8/18/1981) (Box > 6)
- JOHNNY RYAN, (5/4/1984) (Box >210)
- JOURNEY FROM DARKNESS, (12/21/1974) (Box >108)
  Writers: Dick, Peggy Chantler
- JUDGE DEE AND THE MONASTERY MURDERS, (2/5/1974) (Box >170)
  Writers: Meyer, Nicholas; Van Gulik, Robert
- JUDGE NO THE ANGRY, (no date) (Box >197)
  Writers: Grenier, Geo
- JUDGEMENT, (10/13/1989) (Box >174)
  Writers: Topor, Tom
- JUNIOR IN LOVE (Released as Problem Child 3: Junior in Love, (1/18/1995) (Box >256)
  Writers: Hitchcock, Michael
- JURY DUTY: THE COMEDY, (5/1/1989) (Box >101)
  Writers: Gilmer, Rob
- JURY DUTY: THE COMEDY, (5/22/1989) (Box > 74)
- JUST IN CASE, (1/14/1988) (Box > 66)
  Writers: Edwards, Blake; Edwards, Blake (concept by)
- JUST ME AND YOU, (12/12/1977) (Box > 48)
  Writers: Lasser, L.
- JUSTICE IN A SMALL TOWN, (no date) (Box >216)
  Writers: Rasheke, Richard
- KANE & ABEL (PART I), (6/25/1984) (Box > 48)
- KANE & ABEL (PART I, II, III), (12/11/1984) (Box > 48)
  Writers: Lenski, R.
- KANE & ABEL (PART II), (6/25/1984) (Box > 1)
- KANE & ABEL (PART III), (7/3/1984) (Box > 48)
- KANE & ABLE (PART I), (1/25/1985) (Box >191)
- KANE & ABLE (PART I), (no date) (Box >192)
- KANSAS, (11/1/1993) (Box >207)
  Writers: Ashford, Michelle
- KANSAS CITY MASSACRE, (12/9/1974) (Box > 13)
  Writers: Hardman, R.
- KANSAS GOTHIC (PARTS I AND II), (12/9/1986) (Box > 68)
  Writers: Robe, Mike
- KAREN CARPENTER STORY (THE): A SONG FOR YOU, (12/24/1987) (Box > 66)
- KATE BLISS AND THE TICKER TAPE KID, (9/23/1977) (Box >117)
- KATE McSHANE, (1/24/1975) (Box > 89)
- KATHERINE, (4/4/1975) (Box >130)
  Writers: Kagan, Jeremy Paul
- KATHERINE, (5/1/1975) (Box >170)
  Writers: Kagan, Jeremy
- KATHIE LEE GIFFORD CHRISTMAS SPECIAL, (no date) (Box >229)
- KATIE: PORTRAIT OF CENTERFOLD, (5/25/1978) (Box > 48)
  Writers: Audley, N.; Bassinger, Kim
- KEEFER, (3/31/1977) (Box >117)
  Writers: Driskill, Bill; Muntner, Simon
- KEEFER, (6/20/1977) (Box >175)
- KEEGANS (THE), (2/10/1975) (Box >202)
  Writers: Riesner, Dean
- KENNEDY (PART I), (no date) (Box >151)
  Writers: Gadney, Reg
- KENNEDY (PART II), (no date) (Box >151)
- KENNEDY (PART III), (no date) (Box >151)
- KENNEDY (PART IV), (no date) (Box >151)
- KENNEDY (PART V), (no date) (Box >151)
- KENNEDY (PART VI), (no date) (Box >151)
- KENNEDY (PART VII), (no date) (Box >151)
- KENT STATE, (8/3/1980) (Box > 94)
  Writers: Green, Gerald; Kramer, Richard
- KICKS, (9/20/1984) (Box >188)
- KICKS, (11/5/1984) (Box >112)
- KID FROM LEFT FIELD (THE), (6/4/1979) (Box >132)
  Writers: Powers, Katherine
- KID FROM NOWHERE (THE), (1/4/1982) (Box > 20)
- KIDS DON'T TELL, (6/12/1984) (Box >189)
  Writers: Silverman, Peter; Hurley, Maurice
- KIDS DON'T TELL, (2/28/1984) (Box > 80)
  Writers: Hurley, Maurice; Silverman, Peter
- KILL ME IF YOU CAN, (12/29/1976) (Box >133)
- KILL ME IF YOU CAN, (11/3/1976) (Box >133)
- KILLER BY NIGHT, (1/28/1971) (Box >149)
  Writers: Harmon, David P.
- KILLING AFFAIR, A (AKA D.H.Q.), (4/5/1977) (Box > 66)
  Writers: Kean Arthur, E.
- KILLING AT HELL'S GATE, (5/18/1981) (Box >116)
  Writers: Hutson, Lee
- KILLJOY, (5/27/1981) (Box > 94)
  Writers: Rolfe, Sam H.
- KING CRAB, (no date) (Box > 6)
- KING CRAB, (1/30/1980) (Box > 71)
  Writers: Ransone, Preston
- KINGFISH, (12/8/1993) (Box >204)
  Writers: Monash, Paul; Long, Huey P. (story)
- KING'S ROW, (6/13/1980) (Box > 48)
  Writers: Bellaman, H.
- KINGSTON, (4/12/1976) (Box >242)
  Writers: Nelson, Dick; Victor, David
- KISS MEETS THE PHANTOM, (4/19/1978) (Box >115)
  Writers: Sherman, Jan-Michael; Buday, Don
- KISS SHOT, (9/29/1988) (Box > 65)
  Writers: Kleinschmidt, Carl
- LACE (PART I), (8/15/1983) (Box >159)
  Writers: Baker, Elliott
- LACE (PART I), (9/14/1983) (Box >159)
  Writers: Baker, Elliot
- LACE (PART II), (9/14/1983) (Box >159)
- LACE (PART II), (8/24/1983) (Box >159)
- LACE I (PART I), (6/20/1983) (Box > 49)
  Writers: Baker, E.
- LACE II (PART I), (9/21/1984) (Box > 49)
- LACE II (PART I), (10/10/1984) (Box >196)
- LACE II (PART I), (10/10/1984) (Box > 49)
- LACE II (PART I), (8/12/1984) (Box > 49)
- LACE II (PART II), (9/21/1984) (Box > 49)
- LACE II (PART II), (10/10/1984) (Box > 49)
- LACE II (PART II), (10/10/1984) (Box >196)
- LACE II (PART II), (9/1/1984) (Box > 49)
- LACY AND THE MISSISSIPPI QUEEN, (1/27/1978) (Box >117)
  Writers: Donnell, Kathy; Wagner, Madeline DeMaggio
- LACY AND THE MISSISSIPPI QUEEN, (3/14/1978) (Box >154)
  Writers: Donnell, Kathy; Wagner, Madeline DiMaggio
- LADY FORM YESTERDAY (THE), (1/22/1982) (Box >187)
  Writers: Maschler, Tim; Pettus, Ken
- LADY FROM YESTERDAY (THE), (no date) (Box > 20)
- LADY OF THE HOUSE, (1/1/1978) (Box > 87)
  Writers: Koslow, Ron
- LAKOTA WOMAN, (9/16/1994) (Box >200)
  Writers: Waters, Tersa L
- LARRY, (2/19/1974) (Box >120)
  Writers: Seltzer, David
- LAST CHILD (THE), (1/26/1971) (Box >106)
  Writers: Fischer, Peter S.
- LAST DAY (THE), (12/17/1974) (Box > 90)
  Writers: Byrnes, Jim; Fisher, Steve; Lyles, A.C.
- LAST DAY OF PATTON (THE), (no date) (Box > 20)
- LAST DAYS OF POMPEII (THE), (8/10/1979) (Box > 50)
  Writers: Culver, C.
- LAST ELECTRIC KNIGHT (THE), (8/30/1985) (Box >184)
- LAST FLING (THE), (6/11/1986) (Box >168)
  Writers: Katlin, Mitchel Lee
- LAST FLING (THE) [INCOMPLETE], (6/2/1986) (Box >176)
- LAST FRONTIER (THE), (4/21/1986) (Box > 32)
  Writers: Laurence, Michaal
- LAST FRONTIER (THE) (PART I), (1/10/1986) (Box > 1)
  Writers: Laurence, Michael; Dunn, Roger
- LAST FRONTIER (THE) (PART II), (1/10/1986) (Box > 1)
  Writers: Laurence, Michael; Mistp, John
- LAST HURRAH (THE), (4/12/1977) (Box > 88)
  Writers: O'Conner, Carroll; O'Conner, Edwin
- LAST INNOCENT MAN (THE), (no date) (Box > 16)
  Writers: Bronson, Dan; Margolin, Phillip
- LAST LIGHT, (no date) (Box >137)
  Writers: Eisele, Robert
- LAST OF HIS TRIBE (THE), (9/10/1991) (Box >204)
  Writers: Harrigan, Stephen
- LAST OF THE GOOD GUYS (THE), (10/21/1977) (Box >117)
  Writers: Hess, John D.; Flicker, Theodore J.
- LAST OUTLAW (THE), (2/14/1993) (Box >245)
  Writers: Red, Eric
- LAST PROSTITUTE (THE), (6/14/1990) (Box >183)
  Writers: Culver, Carmen
- LAST RIDE OF THE DALTON GANG (THE), (4/10/1978) (Box >114)
  Writers: Wallace, Earl W.
- LAST SONG (THE), (12/7/1979) (Box >178)
- LAST STAND AT SABER RIVER, (4/10/1996) (Box >217)
  Writers: Cohen, Ronald M.
- LAST SURVIVORS (THE), (11/30/1974) (Box >147)
- LATE CHRISTOPHER BEAN (THE), (7/13/1984) (Box > 50)
  Writers: Kirgo, G.
- LATE CHRISTOPHER BEAN (THE), (6/15/1984) (Box > 50)
- LATE SHIFT (THE), (4/13/1995) (Box >228)
  Writers: Carter, Bill
- LATE SHIFT (THE), (4/13/1995) (Box >220)
- LATHE OF HEAVEN, (no date) (Box > 6)
- LAW (THE), (2/4/1974) (Box >242)
  Writers: Oliansky, Joel; Sackheim, William
- LAW AND ORDER, (12/29/1975) (Box >166)
- LAW OF THE LAND, (1/23/1976) (Box >165)
- LEAP OF FAITH, (10/26/1987) (Box >129)
  Writers: Hart, Bruce
- LEAVE YESTERDAY BEHIND, (2/24/1978) (Box >182)
  Writers: Harrison, Paul; Wilson, Elizabeth
- LEAVE YESTERDAY BEHIND, (1/16/1978) (Box >121)
- LEGALESE, (2/15/1995) (Box >256)
  Writers: Ray, Billy
- LEGEND OF LIZZIE BORDEN (THE), (9/25/1974) (Box > 50)
  Writers: Bast, W.
- LEGEND OF LIZZIE BORDEN (THE), (10/18/1974) (Box >151)
- LEGEND OF WALKS FAR WOMAN (THE), (7/20/1979) (Box > 96)
- LEGS, (11/29/1982) (Box >138)
- LETTER (THE), (3/16/1981) (Box >203)
  Writers: Marcus, Lawrence B
- LETTER TO THREE WIVES, A, (7/9/1984) (Box > 51)
  Writers: Robinson, S.
- LETTERS (THE), (12/28/1972) (Box >144)
- LETTERS (THE), (10/28/1972) (Box >250)
- LETTERS FROM THREE LOVERS, (6/21/1973) (Box >106)
  Writers: Marcus, Ann; Kass, Jerome
- LIBERATORS (THE), (8/25/1986) (Box > 30)
  Writers: JOHNSON, KENNETH
- LIBERATORS (THE), (6/17/1986) (Box >142)
- LIBERTY, (no date) (Box > 20)
- LIBERTY WEEKEND CLOSING CEREMONIES (Special), (no date) (Box >233)
- LICENSE TO KILL, (4/26/1991) (Box >136)
  Writers: Schwartz, William A.; Robe, Mike
- LIFE GOES TO THE MOVIES, (no date) (Box >256)
  Writers: Schickel, Richard
- LIFE OF THE PARTY (THE), (6/18/1979) (Box > 6)
- LIKE MOM, LIKE ME, (3/7/1978) (Box >176)
  Writers: Schwartz, Nancy Lynn; Schwartz, Sheila
- LILY IN WINTER, (7/25/1994) (Box >209)
- LISTEN TO YOUR HEART, (5/25/1982) (Box >121)
  Writers: Beaumont, Christopher
- LITTLE GAME, A, (6/29/1971) (Box >202)
- LITTLE GIRL LOST, (1/28/1974) (Box > 80)
  Writers: Ware, Clyde
- LITTLE GIRL LOST, (12/2/1980) (Box > 33)
  Writers: Lane, Brian; Title, Susan
- LITTLE GLORIA, HAPPY AT LAST, (4/29/1982) (Box >102)
  Writers: Bergen, Robert
- LITTLE GLORIA, HAPPY AT LAST (PART I, II), (no date) (Box > 51)
  Writers: Hanley, W.
- LITTLE GLORIA-HAPPY AT LAST (PART I), (3/18/1982) (Box >192)
- LITTLE GLORIA-HAPPY AT LAST (PART II), (3/18/1982) (Box >192)
- LITTLE MO, (1/24/1978) (Box >115)
- LITTLE SISTER, (no date) (Box > 33)
  Writers: Simmons, Anthony
- LITTLE SISTER, (12/6/1982) (Box > 7)
- LIVE WIRE, (10/8/1991) (Box >124)
  Writers: Baker, Bart
- LIVING A LIE, (12/9/1990) (Box >208)
  Writers: Bernhardt, Sharon; Freistat, Lana
- LIVING PROOF: THE HANK WILLIAMS, JR. STORY, (12/21/1981) (Box > 33)
  Writers: KANDEL, STEPHEN
- LIVING PROOF: THE HANK WILLIAMS, JR. STORY, (4/8/1981) (Box > 72)
  Writers: Rapoport, I. C.; Williams, Hank Jr.
- LIVING PROOF: THE HANK WILLIAMS, JR. STORY, (6/1/1982) (Box >148)
- LOIS GIBBS AND THE LOVE CANAL, (9/30/1981) (Box >164)
- LONE STAR KID (THE) (SPECIAL), (11/1/1985) (Box >244)
  Writers: Williams, Anson; Hiser, Barbara
- LONELIEST RUNNER (THE), (8/15/1976) (Box >163)
  Writers: Landon, Michael
- LONESOME DOVE (PARTS I-IV), (3/16/1987) (Box >102)
  Writers: Wittliff, Bill
- LONG GONE, (5/23/1977) (Box > 20)
- LONG HOT SUMMER (THE) (PART I), (5/11/1984) (Box > 51)
  Writers: Brown, R.M.
- LONG HOT SUMMER (THE) (PART II), (9/13/1984) (Box > 51)
- LONG JOURNEY BACK (THE), (7/24/1978) (Box > 83)
  Writers: Levin, Audrey Davis
- LONG JOURNEY HOME (THE), (5/28/1987) (Box > 31)
  Writers: Clark, Karen
- LONG SHADOWS, (no date) (Box >242)
  Writers: Stitt, Milan
- LONG SUMMER OF GEORGE ADAMS (THE), (no date) (Box > 20)
- LOOK OF THE YEAR 1988 (Special), (no date) (Box >232)
- LOOSE CANNON, (2/21/1989) (Box > 31)
  Writers: Hargrove, Dean
- LOST FLIGHT, (11/7/1966) (Box >251)
- LOU RAWLS PARADE OF STARS (Special), (no date) (Box >221)
- LOUIS ARMSTRONG: CHICAGO STYLE, (no date) (Box >120)
  Writers: Lee, James
- LOUIS ARMSTRONG: CHICAGO STYLE, (no date) (Box >132)
- LOUIS ARMSTRONG: CHICAGO STYLE, (no date) (Box >132)
- LOUIS L'AMOUR'S DOWN THE LONG HILLS, (5/12/1986) (Box >160)
  Writers: L'Amour, Louis
- LOVE AFFAIR, A: THE ELEANOR AND LOU GEHRIG STORY, (4/5/1977) (Box >149)
- LOVE AMONG THE RUINS, (4/29/1974) (Box >143)
- LOVE AMONG THE RUINS, (5/21/1974) (Box >101)
- LOVE BOAT II (THE), (11/23/1976) (Box >185)
  Writers: Aldredge, Dawn; Freeman, Marion C.
- LOVE IS FOREVER, (no date) (Box > 88)
  Writers: Bartlett, Hall
- LOVE IS...BARBARA EDEN (SPECIAL), (no date) (Box >244)
- LOVE LEADS THAT WAY, (10/7/1984) (Box > 21)
- LOVE LEADS THE WAY, (1/20/1984) (Box >157)
  Writers: Denker, Henry
- LOVE LIVES ON, (12/17/1984) (Box >158)
- LOVE LIVES ON, (10/3/1984) (Box > 25)
- LOVE WAR (THE), (10/3/1969) (Box >132)
  Writers: Trueblood, Guerdon; Kidd, David
- LOVE, CHEAT AND STEEL, (no date) (Box >138)
  Writers: Curran, William B.
- LOVE, LIES AND MURDER, (5/12/1990) (Box >155)
  Writers: Hill, Danielle
- LOVE, LIES AND MURDER, (5/25/1990) (Box >125)
- LOVE, MARY, (no date) (Box > 21)
- LOVECRAFT, (no date) (Box >110)
- LOVE'S DARK RIDE, (11/23/1977) (Box >109)
  Writers: Frankel, Ernie; Beckett, Ann
- LOVE'S SAVAGE FURY, (no date) (Box > 21)
- LUCAN, (2/16/1977) (Box >152)
- LUCAN, (1/14/1977) (Box > 7)
- LUCILLE BALL SPECIAL (THE) (SPECIAL), (7/18/1977) (Box >243)
  Writers: Carroll, Bob Jr.; Davis, Madelyn
- LUCILLE BALL SPECIAL, A (SPECIAL), (no date) (Box >243)
- LUCY AND DESI: BEFORE THE LAUGHTER, (7/19/1990) (Box >125)
  Writers: Luce, William; Cherbak, Cynthia A.
- LUCY GETS LUCKY (SPECIAL), (11/18/1974) (Box >243)
  Writers: O'Brien, Bob
- LYNDA CARTER SPECIAL V, (no date) (Box >232)
  Writers: Arnott, Bob
- M.A.D.D.: MOTHERS AGAINST DRUNK DRIVERS, (10/21/1982) (Box >134)
- MAD BULL, (6/17/1977) (Box >246)
  Writers: Zimmerman, Vernon
- MAD BULL, (5/23/1977) (Box > 79)
- MADE IN U.S.A. (Special), (no date) (Box >224)
- MAE WEST, (12/11/1981) (Box >137)
  Writers: Kean, E. Arthur
- MAGIC OF DAVID COPPERFIELD (THE), (3/19/1984) (Box >253)
  Writers: Bormet, Garry; Slocum, Frank
- MAKING OF A MALE MODEL (THE), (4/20/1983) (Box >140)
  Writers: Carolthers, A.J.
- MALIBU (PART I), (7/1/1982) (Box > 51)
- MALICE IN WONDERLAND, (12/18/1984) (Box >149)
  Writers: Seidler, David; Feather, Jacqueline
- MAN FROM U.N.C.L.E. (THE), (no date) (Box > 72)
  Writers: Short, Robert Y.; Biederman, Danny
- MAN HUNTERS (THE), (no date) (Box > 51)
  Writers: Noxon, N.
- MAN IN THE SANTA CLAUS SUIT (THE), (9/21/1979) (Box > 97)
  Writers: Kirgo, George; Gershe, Leonard (story by)
- MAN WHO COULD TALK TO KIDS (THE), (4/13/1973) (Box >140)
- MAN WHO LIVED AT THE RITZ (THE) (PART I), (2/8/1988) (Box > 70)
- MAN WHO LIVED AT THE RITZ (THE) (PART II), (3/2/1988) (Box > 70)
- MAN WITH THE POWE (THE), (2/25/1977) (Box >198)
  Writers: Balter, Allan
- MANDRAKE THE MAGICIAN, (no date) (Box > 21)
- MANEATERS ARE LOOSE!, (1/9/1978) (Box >109)
- MANIONS OF AMERICA (THE) (PART II), (11/28/1980) (Box >162)
  Writers: Sisson, Rosemary Anne; Nixon, Agnes
- MANIONS OF AMERICA (THE) (PART III), (1/1/1981) (Box >162)
- MANITOU (THE), (3/7/1977) (Box > 7)
- MARATHON, (8/20/1979) (Box >113)
  Writers: Friedman, Ron; Rapaport, Charles
- MARCIANO (FORMERLY: I'LL GET BY...), (4/17/1979) (Box >104)
- MARCUS-NELSON MURDERS (THE), (no date) (Box >130)
  Writers: Mann, Abby
- MARCUS-NELSON MURDERS (THE), (10/31/1972) (Box >178)
- MARIAN ROSE WHITE, (3/10/1981) (Box >163)
  Writers: Rusoff, Garry
- MARILYN AND BOBBY: HER E-MAIL AFFAIR, (2/9/1993) (Box >213)
  Writers: Macdonald, Gerard
- MARILYN: THE UNTOLD STORY, (12/27/1979) (Box > 83)
  Writers: Young, Dalene; Mailer, Norman
- MARILYN: THE UNTOLD STORY, (3/26/1980) (Box > 91)
  Writers: Young, Dalene; Eliason, Joyce; Mailer, Norman
- MARK, I LOVE YOU, (7/25/1980) (Box >191)
  Writers: Grafton, Sue
- MARLA HANSON STORY (THE), (9/24/1990) (Box >125)
  Writers: Gray, John
- MARRIAGE IS ALIVE AND WELL, (9/5/1979) (Box >100)
- MARSHAEL (THE), (1/20/1994) (Box >201)
  Writers: Mankiewicz, John; Pyne, Daniel
- MARTIAN CHRONICLES (THE) (PARTS I, II, III), (no date) (Box > 51)
  Writers: Matheson, R.
- MARY AND JOSEPH: A STORY OF FAITH, (no date) (Box >146)
- MARY WHITE, (3/11/1976) (Box > 79)
- MASADA, (11/30/1979) (Box >199)
  Writers: Oliansky Joel
- MASADA, (5/18/1979) (Box > 52)
  Writers: Oliansky, J.
- MASERATI AND THE BRAIN, (1/29/1982) (Box > 7)
- MATTER OF DEATH AND LIFE, A, (5/28/1980) (Box >107)
- MATTER OF SEX, A, (6/10/1982) (Box > 52)
  Writers: Eliason, J.
- MATTER OF SEX, A, (11/10/1982) (Box >147)
- MAX AND HELEN, (2/11/1988) (Box > 73)
- MAX AND SON, (9/6/1979) (Box > 52)
  Writers: Fairman, M.
- MAYBE I'LL COME HOME IN THE SPRING, (9/4/1970) (Box > 88)
  Writers: Feldman, Bruce
- MEDUSA'S CHILD (FIRST NIGHT), (3/17/1997) (Box >218)
  Writers: Weston, Ellen
- MEDUSA'S CHILD (SECOND NIGHT), (3/17/1997) (Box >218)
- MELVIN PURVIS: G-MAN, (1/29/1974) (Box >143)
  Writers: Nolan, William F.; Milius, John
- MEMPHIS, (no date) (Box > 91)
  Writers: Mcmurtry, Larry; Shepherd, Cybil; Foote, Shelby
- MEN OF THE DRAGON, (12/21/1973) (Box >118)
  Writers: Petitclerc, Denne Bart
- MERCY OR MURDER?, (10/2/1986) (Box >186)
- MIDAS VALLEY, (12/13/1983) (Box > 81)
  Writers: Beckett, Ann
- MIDDLE AGES, (1/1/1992) (Box >201)
  Writers: Rogow, Stan; Byrum, John
- MIDNIGHT HOUR (THE), (7/29/1985) (Box >112)
- MIDNIGHT OFFERINGS, (1/8/1981) (Box >140)
  Writers: Bartlett, Juanita